Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 15, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Impact Upon Small Business of Dual Distribution and Related Vertical Integration, 1964; Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Notes: December 30, 1964
- Box: 15, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: CETA/SESA Guide, 1975; Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Notes: June 1975
- Box: 15, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Proposed Bill and Supporting Report on Employee-Management Relations in the Public Service, 1962; Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Author: Anthony P. Savarese
  - Item 2: The Condon-Wadlin Law in New York State, 1953; Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Author: Nim Chee Siew
  - Item 3: Report on Condon-Wadlin Act, 1955; Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Author: Commerce and Industry Association of New York, Inc.
    Notes: March 14, 1955
- Box: 15, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Full-Time Police & Fire Personnel in Connecticut, 1965; Publication (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Author: Connecticut Public Expenditure Council
  - Item 2: The Candy Industry, 1946; Publication (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Author: Calvin K. Kazanjian
  - Item 3: A Brief History of Industrial Development in Connecticut, 1948; Publication (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Author: James K. Finch
- Box: 15, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The American Ultras: The Extreme Right and the Military-Industrial Complex, 1962; Publication (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Author: Irwin Suall
- Box: 15, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Victims of Merger Fever, Publication (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Author: Roger Sheldon
- Box: 15, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Merger Issue in the United States, Publication (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Box: 15, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Injuries and Accident Analysis in Contract Construction, 1961; Publication (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Author: Edmond M. Boggs
- Box: 15, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Accident Hazards and Costs in the Construction Industry, Publication (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Author: Workmen's Compensation Board
  - Item 2: An Act to Amend the Construction Hoists Act, 1960-61, 1963; Publication (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Box: 15, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Men on Site: Ten Case Studies in Building Management, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Author: Department of Employment and Productivity
  - Item 2: Direct Labour and the Rates, Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Author: Malcolm Hoppe
  - Item 3: Operatives in the Building Industry, 1968; Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Author: Geoffrey Thomas
- Box: 15, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Federal Laws Relating to Employment of Labor in Construction, 1962; Publication (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Author: The Associated General Contractors of America
- Box: 15, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Building Workers in Israel, 1946-1969, Publication (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Author: M Amster
- Box: 15, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Employment Distribution Study of the Construction Industry in Michigan, 1966; Publication (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Box: 15, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Manpower Requirements in the Construction Industry in Nova Scotia, 1966; Publication (Box 15, Folder 25)
    Author: N. Layton Fergusson
- Box: 15, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: A Safety Program for Building Trades Unions, 1927; Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Author: Workers' Health Bureau of America
    Notes: June 18-19, 1927
- Box: 15, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Byggnadsindustrins Arbetsproduktivitet, 1967; Publication (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Author: Egnellska Boktryckeriet
- Box: 15, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Trundle Service, 1949; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Author: The Trundle Engineering Company
  - Item 2: Biography of Experience, 1946; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Author: Wallace Clark & Company
    Notes: 1920-1946
  - Item 3: Wage Incentives and Cost Control, 1947; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Author: McClure, Hadden & Ortman, Inc.
    Notes: February 5-7, 1947
  - Item 4: What's Ahead in Paying Salesmen?, 1948; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Cleats, 1949; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: Business Research Corporation, 1948; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Author: Business Research Corporation
  - Item 7: Trundle Talks No. 123, 1949; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Author: Trundle Engineering Co.
  - Item 8: Developing Greater Productivity Through Internal Public Relations, 1947; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Author: Robert M. Creaghead & Company
  - Item 9: Auditing Your Man Hours, 1947; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: Addresses and Papers Delivered and Read at the Labor-Management Relations Conference, 1944; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Author: Barnes Textile Associates, Inc.
    Notes: June 7 & 8, 1944
  - Item 11: Profit on Net Worth: Continuing the Analysis of the Profit Structure, 1940; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Author: Stevenson, Jordan& Harrison, Inc.
  - Item 12: The Human Factor in Industry, 1949; Publication (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Notes: March 23, 1949
- Box: 15, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: How to Get the Best Results from Management Consultants, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    Author: Philip W. Shay
  - Item 2: How to Get the Best Results from Management Consultants, 1965; Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Acme Survey on Compensation for Professional Staff in Management Consulting Firms, 1967; Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: An Outline of the Scope of the Services Rendered, and Our Personnel, Professional Qualifications and Experience, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    Author: George S. Armstrong & Co., Inc.
- Box: 15, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Delays and Disputes in Building Construction, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Construction Industry Under the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1973; Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Notes: February 1973
  - Item 3: Labor Requirements for Hospital Construction, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Opportunity Limited: A Guide for Veterans Interested in the Construction Industry, 1945; Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Author: Van Rensselaer Sill
    Notes: December 1945
  - Item 5: Construction and Construction Materials, Industry Report; Special Feature: State Construction Activity, 1947, 1948; Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Author: U.S. Bureau of Foreign and Domestic Commerce
  - Item 6: A Survey of Minority Construction Contractors, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Author: U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development
  - Item 7: Looking Ahead with the Construction Industry, 1946; Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Author: The Producers' Council, Inc
    Notes: September 25 & 26, 1946
  - Item 8: Construction Industry Controls, 1947; Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Author: Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America
    Notes: January 20, 1947
  - Item 9: Summary of Proceedings, The Construction Industry Advisory Council, 1946; Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Author: The Construction Industry Advisory Council
    Notes: November 20-21, 1946
  - Item 10: Stabilizing the Contruction Industry, 1945; Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Author: Miles L. Colean
    Notes: February 1945
- Box: 15, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Statistics on Construction: A Program for Improvement, 1970; Publication (Box 15, Folder 31)
    Author: Cabinet Committee on Construction
- Box: 15, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Credit Practices of Retailers and Financers of Furniture and Home Appliances in Two Northwest Cities, 1963; Publication (Box 15, Folder 32)
    Author: University of Idaho
- Box: 15, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: A Guide to Consumer Credit, 1963; Publication (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Box: 15, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Consumer Education for Low-Income Families; A Limited Survey of Programs and Resources, 1964; Publication (Box 15, Folder 34)
    Author: Consumers Union of U.S., Inc.
  - Item 2: Consumer Protective Movements on the State and Local Levels -- 1963, Publication (Box 15, Folder 34)
    Author: Colston E. Warne
- Box: 15, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Sources of Consumer Information, Publication (Box 15, Folder 35)
    Author: New York State Department of Commerce Woman's Program
  - Item 2: Consumer Behavior in 1961, A Summary Report, Publication (Box 15, Folder 35)
    Author: Foundation for Research on Human Behavior
- Box: 15, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: A Federal Department of Consumers, and Related Proposals, 1962; Publication (Box 15, Folder 36)
    Notes: February 9, 1962
- Box: 15, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Impact of the War on Civilian Consumption, 1945; Publication (Box 15, Folder 37)
    Author: Combined Production and Resources Board
    Notes: September 1945
  - Item 2: The Consumer of the Seventies, 1969; Publication (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: Report of the Commission of Inquiry into the System of Contract Labour in Singapore, 1960; Publication (Box 15, Folder 37)
    Author: State of Singapore
- Box: 16, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Prison Industries and Rehabilitation Programs, 1959; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: Ernest E. Means
- Box: 16, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Work for Prisoner; Report, 1961; Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Author: Great Britain Home Office and Scottish Home Department
- Box: 16, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Co-Operatives: True or False, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Author: J.A. Hough
- Box: 16, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Quiet Revolution; A Study of the Antigonism Movement, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Author: Harold Lewack
- Box: 16, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Short Introduction to Consumers' Cooperation, 1946; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Author: Ellis Cowling
  - Item 2: Economics of Consumer Cooperatives, 1965; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Author: Marian Redetzki
- Box: 16, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Cinquante ans D'Unite Cooperative, 1962; Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Author: Liaisons Cooperatives
    Notes: September 1962
- Box: 16, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Consumer Cooperation as Faith and as Works, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Author: Horace M. Kallen
  - Item 2: A Model Consumer Action Program for Low Income Neighborhoods, 1966; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Author: Harry S. Shadden, JR.
  - Item 3: Effective Self Help: The Buying Club, A first Step in Consumer Group Action, 1966; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Author: Cooperative League of the USA
  - Item 4: Canned Goods Crusader, 1946; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Author: The Cooperative League
- Box: 16, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Dictionary of Cooperation, 1948; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Author: Emory S. Bogardus
- Box: 16, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Consumers' Co-Operation in Norway, 1958; Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Author: Liv Ovesen
    Notes: December 1958
- Box: 16, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Portrait of a Movement, 1967; Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Author: The Co-Operative Union Ltd.
- Box: 16, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Economic Humanism, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Author: H.A. Atkinson
  - Item 2: Interim Report of the Liberal Party Co-Ownership Committee, 1955; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Author: Liberal Publications Department
  - Item 3: Agricultural Cooperatives, 1946; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Statistics of Farmers' Marketing and Purchasing Cooperatives 1945-1946, 1948; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Author: Grace Wanstall
- Box: 16, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitutional Relations Between the Labour and Co-Operative Parties: An Historical Review, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Author: Barbara Smith and Geoffrey Ostergard
- Box: 16, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Cooperatives Look Ahead, 1952; Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Author: Jerry Voorhis
    Notes: July 1952
  - Item 2: Number of Full-Time Employees of Farmer Cooperatives, 1960; Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Author: Nelda Griffin
    Notes: January 1960
  - Item 3: Industrial Cooperation: Possibilities within a Balanced Movement, 1946; Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Author: J.B. Tayler
  - Item 4: Cooperatives in the Petroleum Industry, 1947; Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Author: K.E. Ettinger
  - Item 5: Cooperatives in the Petroleum Industry, 1947; Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Notes: Part One
- Box: 16, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: A Selected and Annotated Bibliography of Literature on Farmer Cooperatives, 1947; Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Author: William A. Nielander
    Notes: October 1947
- Box: 16, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Noticia Do Cooperativismo Brasileiro, 1947; Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Author: Uniao Pan-Americana
    Language: Portuguese.
- Box: 16, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Consumers' Co-Operation in Germany, 1961; Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Author: Erwin Hasselmann
  - Item 2: Die Konsum Genossenschaften in Der Deutschen Demokratischen Republik, 1965; Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Author: Fakten Und Ziffern
- Box: 16, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Social Ownership and Control, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Author: Co-Operative Party
  - Item 2: Regional Plan for Co-Operative Societies in England, Wales, and Ireland, 1968; Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Portrait of a Movement, 1961; Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Box: 16, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Co-Operation, 1962; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Author: W.R.S. Satthianadhan & J.C. Ryan
- Box: 16, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Das Genossenschaftswesen in der Sowjetunion, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Author: Arnolds Aizsilnieks
    Notes: December 1950
- Box: 16, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Las Cooperativas Como Metodo de Desarrollo de Regiones y Comunidades, 1964; Publication (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Author: Union Panamericana
- Box: 16, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Problems of Cooperation, 1960; Publication (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: The A.B.C. of Co-op Finance, Publication (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Author: Leslie A. Woodcock
  - Item 3: Tax Liability of Cooperatives, Publication (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Author: Commerce and Industry Association of Research, Inc.
- Box: 16, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Copper; Basic Industrial Data, 1946; Publication (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Box: 16, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Copper and Lead-Zinc Mining, 1954; Publication (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Box: 16, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Report of the Northern Rhodesia Board of Inquiry on the Advancement of Africans in the Copper Mining Industry in Northern Rhodesia, 1954; Publication (Box 16, Folder 24)
    Author: Rhodesia Government Printer
  - Item 2: Report of the Northern Rhodesia Commission Appointed to Inquire into the Minint Industry in Northern Rhodesia, 1962; Publication (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Box: 16, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Copyright Law of the United States of America, 1960; Publication (Box 16, Folder 25)
    Author: U.S. Copyright Office
  - Item 2: Copyright Law of the United States of America, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Box: 16, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Cordage Business, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 26)
    Author: William A. Scherff
- Box: 16, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Authorities as a Governmental Technique, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 27)
    Author: Austin J. Tobin
    Notes: March 26, 1953
- Box: 16, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Managing a Business with the Help of Printing, 1961; Publication (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Author: S.D. Warren Company
  - Item 2: How to Read an Annual Report, Publication (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Author: Stuart Chase
  - Item 3: What Makes an Annual Report Effective, 1965; Publication (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Where Good Annual Report Practice is Going, 1957; Publication (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Notes: November 1957
- Box: 16, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Boards of Directors, Publication (Box 16, Folder 29)
    Author: Herrymon Maurer
  - Item 2: The Company Secretary, 1963; Publication (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Box: 16, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Working Capital of 1186 Registered Corporations, 1946; Publication (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Author: Securities and Exchange Commission
    Notes: November 4, 1946
  - Item 2: The Functional Operating Report Manual, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Author: Robert R. Doane & Joseph E. Canning
  - Item 3: Annual Report to Employees, 1940; Publication (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: The Corporation and the Republic, 1958; Publication (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Author: Scott Buchanan
  - Item 5: Politics and the Corporation, 1958; Publication (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Author: Andrew Hacker
- Box: 16, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: How to Choose a Correspondence School, 1959; Publication (Box 16, Folder 31)
    Author: Homer Kempfer
  - Item 2: Home Study Blue Book, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 31)
    Author: National Home Study Council
- Box: 16, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: The Manual of Standards, 1947; Publication (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Box: 16, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Accounting for Management; an Introduction to Costing and Cost Control, 1951; Publication (Box 16, Folder 33)
    Author: British Association for Commercial and Industrial Education
    Notes: Spring 1951
  - Item 2: Cost of Accounting and Productivity in the USA, 1952; Publication (Box 16, Folder 33)
    Author: Organisation for European Economic Co-Operation
  - Item 3: How to Use Standard Cost, 1952; Publication (Box 16, Folder 33)
    Author: John Pugsley
  - Item 4: Program Analysis Techniques: A Selected Bibliography, 1966; Publication (Box 16, Folder 33)
    Author: U.S. Bureau of the Budget
- Box: 16, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: How Companies Get Costs Down Through Teamwork, 1954; Publication (Box 16, Folder 34)
    Notes: August 1954
  - Item 2: Getting Employee Help on Cutting Costs, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 34)
    Notes: August 1953
  - Item 3: How Companies Get Costs Down Through Teamwork, 1954; Publication (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: Getting Employee Help on Cutting Costs, 1953; Publication (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Item 5: Creativity vs. Convormity in Management, 1959; Publication (Box 16, Folder 34)
    Notes: June 1959
- Box: 16, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: A New Tool for Office Salary Determination, Publication (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Work Time Required to Buy Food in the USA and Eleven Other Countries in 1951-52, Publication (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Work Time Required to Buy Food, 1937-50, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 35)
    Notes: February 1951
- Box: 16, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Industrial Feeding of African Workers, 1962; Publication (Box 16, Folder 36)
    Author: Carl Keyter
- Box: 16, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Bibliography of Literature on Changes in the Cost of Living and Wage Adjustments, 1939; Publication (Box 16, Folder 37)
    Notes: December, 1939
- Box: 16, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Budget for a Self-Supporting Working Woman, 1961; Publication (Box 16, Folder 38)
    Author: California Industrial Welfare Commission
  - Item 2: Budget for a Single Working Woman, 1950; Publication (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Box: 16, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: A Guide to Family Spending in Toronto, Canada, 1949; Publication (Box 16, Folder 39)
    Author: Welfare Council of Greater Toronto
  - Item 2: The Five Point Program to Increase Consumer Purchasing Power, 1947; Publication (Box 16, Folder 39)
    Author: Workers' Educational Association
    Notes: December 1947
  - Item 3: Summary Tables of "A Guide to Famaly Spending", 1952; Publication (Box 16, Folder 39)
    Notes: February 1, 1952
- Box: 16, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: The Standard of Living in Britain, Publication (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Box: 16, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: A Study of Earnings and Spending of Families of Wage Earners and Clerical Workers on the Islands of Hawaii, Maui, Kauai, 1944; Publication (Box 16, Folder 41)
    Author: Hawaii Department of Labor and Industrial Relations
  - Item 2: Cost of Living in Honolulu, 1940-1948, Publication (Box 16, Folder 41)
    Author: Hawaii Employers Council Research Department
  - Item 3: Cost of Living in Honolulu, 1940-1948, Publication (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Box: 17, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Cost of Living of Male Minors Compared with that of Women Workers, 1944, 1945; Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Comments on Labor Department's Cost of Living Surveys, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Box: 17, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Profit, Income & Living Standards, 1946; Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Author: Institute of Public Affairs
  - Item 2: Soviet Union: Fixed State-Store Prices of Selected Consumer Goods in Moscow, 1949; Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Author: Office of Foreign Labor Conditions
    Notes: March 1, 1949
  - Item 3: This Cost of Living Business, 1951; Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Author: Labour Party
    Notes: January 1951
- Box: 17, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Minimum Budget for a Single Employed Woman in Washington, 1947; Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Author: Washington State Department of Labor and Industries
    Notes: May 5-10, 1947
- Box: 17, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Estimated Cost of Living Budget for Employed Women in Pennsylvania, 1966; Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Box: 17, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Costs Abroad, Excluding Quarters, 1965; Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Author: U.S. Department of State Indexes of Living
  - Item 2: Costs Abroad, Excluding Quarters, 1967; Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Box: 17, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Working Women's Budgets in Twelve States, 1948; Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Annual Review of the Cost of Living, 1940, 1941; Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Notes: January 30, 1941